{
    "id": "7676cda10eb04c9193ef1a5b5ca8f7d2",
    "title": "Make Meaningful Sentences",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ................................. a story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is reading",
                "are reading",
                "has reading"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "749c9baf611d4b7ea73ccf712f98263c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ........................................ for his father.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "is waiting",
                "has waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d2aa326dc9ad4e0f8a98bbe505475a51"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ................................... at the gate?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is standing",
                "stand",
                "stands"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "355a20dda44b452a8b6e8ad7a6083a57"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ less butter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am eating",
                "are eating",
                "have eating"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df85844217f74088ba3b8dcf83c3a010"
        },
        {
            "question": "My grandmother .......................................... past slowly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was walking",
                "were walking",
                "have walking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a1eb635a8603492b8994a089c041fa12"
        },
        {
            "question": "David ......................................... across a field one sunny morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has strolling",
                "was strolling",
                "are strolling"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94d55e9b7bf9439381ab54ada34efc11"
        },
        {
            "question": "A pair of trousers ....................................... in the cupboard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are hanging",
                "is hanging"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75a39ac0b8ce4d08b7857d2c116feb3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sharon ..................................... from a cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has suffering",
                "is suffering",
                "were suffering"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a75325b3c164613b3de3e242f5ed6ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He .................................. his lessons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is learning",
                "has learning",
                "learn"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9120a8c3fbd8400f8b7c9685501e7472"
        },
        {
            "question": "That child ................................. bigger everyday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is getting",
                "get",
                "has getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0be0b9617bab4ef9aee4d1d7b874ea06"
        }
    ]
}